Guide to the Stanford University, Bing Overseas Studies Program, Records SC0117
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Material: Student Letters, 2007-2013; Accession 2013-083
  - Moscow: Fall Quarter 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Moscow: Winter Quarter 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Oxford: Fall Quarter 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Oxford: Winter Quarter 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Oxford: Spring Quarter 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Paris: Fall Quarter 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Paris: Winter Quarter 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Paris: Spring Quarter 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Santiago: Fall Quarter 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Santiago: Winter Quarter 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Santiago: Spring Quarter 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Additional Material, Accession 2014-038
  - Syllabus: Comparative Politics in Eastern Europe, 1972 Winter (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: William Robert Moore to Professor Robert A. Walker, 1962 May 31 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Additional Material: Student Letters, Accession 2014-049
  - Various Campuses, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH.2014-063
  - The End of Disease, Roger D. Kornberg lecture in Madrid Spain., 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 1)
  - The End of Disease, Roger D. Kornberg lecture in Madrid Spain, promotional material and text of introduction by Santiago Tejerina Canal, 2012 Spring (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH.2014-086
  - The Traffic of Peace: 25th Anniversary of the Krupp Internship Program for Stanford Students in Germany. Delivered at Villa Hugel, Essen, Germany., 2007 May 31 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Overseas Studies: Then and Now. Second Revised Edition., 2013 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH.2014-090
  - "Tibet Deception." Stanford in Germany, Group VI, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Additional Material: Photographs, Accession ARCH.2014-126
  - Italy (students in costume), circa 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Italy (students in costume), circa 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Italy - Florence (Villa il Salviatino), circa 1970s-1980s (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Italy - Florence (Villa il Salviatino), circa 1970s-1980s (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Italy - Florence (group photos at Villa S. Paolo), circa 1960s (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Italy - Florence (students at Villa San Paolo library), 1969 May (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Italy - Florence, circa 1970s (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Italy - Florence (Dr. Scichilone, Tom O'Toole) (Villa Giulia, Etruscan tombs at Tarquinia, Florence view from windows of Villa il Salviatino), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Italy - Florence (students at Villa San Paolo), circa 1970s (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Italy - Florence (Rome field trip), circa 1970s (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Italy - Florence (Prof. Giuseppe Mammarella, director; Leonard Ortolano; etc.), circa 1970s (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Italy - Florence (students at Villa il Salviatino), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Italy - Florence (Rome field trip), circa 1970s-1980s (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Italy - Florence (nearby Florence center), circa 1970s-1980s (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Italy - Florence (students, Ida (cook), Anna Stefano (housekeeper), near the Stanford center), 1988 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Italy - Florence, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Italy - Florence, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Italy - Florence (students), 1990 Jan (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Italy - Florence (faculty apartment), circa 1990s (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Italy - Florence (Russell Berman, director of OSP, etc.), circa 1990s (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Italy - Florence (students at Stanford center), circa 1990s (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Italy - Florence (Giuseppe Mammarella at a conference), circa 1990s (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Italy - Florence (students, Linda Campani), circa 1990s-2000s (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Italy - Florence (Linda Campani; Prof. Morlino; Ana Nicoletti; students) (Stanford center; Carrara Marble), 2000 Mar (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Italy - Florence (Prof. Riccardo Bruscagli, Prof. Antonello LaVergata), 2000 Mar (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Italy - Rome (Intercollegiate Center for Classical Studies), circa 1970s (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Spain - Salamanca, circa 1960s (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Additional Material, Accesssion ARCH.2015-005
  - Krakow (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Academic Services Puebla Program (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Academic Services Puebla Curriculum (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Academic Services Puebla HIV (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Student Exchange Puebla (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Academic Services Puebla Misc. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Other correspondence Mexico (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Mexico Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Puebla Courses (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Puebla Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Puebla Course Information (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Puebla Course Information (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Mexico (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Haifa / Jerusalem (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Paris Program Information (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 2005 Spring Beijing Program Group Keepsake (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - SCTI Alumni Directory, 1900-1999 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Berlin Program Evaluations, Autumn 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Berlin Program Evaluations, Winter 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Berlin Program Evaluations, Spring 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Florence Program Evaluations, Autumn 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Krakow Program Evaluations, Spring 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - SCTI Program Evaluations, 1991-1992 Spring (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Oxford Program Evaluations, 1991-1992 Autumn (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Oxford Program Evaluations, 1991-1992 Winter (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Oxford Program Evaluations, 1991-1992 Spring (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Paris Program Evaluations, 1991-1992 Autumn (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Paris Program Evaluations, 1991-1992 Winter (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Berlin Program Evaluations, 1992-1993 Autumn (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Berlin Program Evaluations, 1992-1993 Winter (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Berlin Program Evaluations, 1992-1993 Spring (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Florence Program Evaluations, 1992-1993 Winter (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Oxford Program Evaluations, 1992-1993 Winter (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Oxford Program Evaluations, 1992-1993 Spring (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Paris Program Evaluations, 1992-1993 Winter (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Moscow Program Evaluations, 1993-1994 Fall (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Course Binders: Program/ Course Descriptions & Syllabi, 1980-1986 (Box 2)
  - Course Binders: Program/ Course Descriptions & Syllabi, 1987-1992 (Box 3)
  - Course Binders: Program/ Course Descriptions & Syllabi, 1992-1998 (Box 4)
  - Course Binders: Program/ Course Descriptions & Syllabi, 1998-2006 (Box 5)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH.2015-064
  - Course Abstracts & Syllabi, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Residential Education and OSP joint plans. To Alice Supton From Nancy Padgett., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Calendar, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Style Guide and Logos (CD) (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2015-135
  - Renovation of Berlin Villa, 1993 (Box 1, Volume 1)
  - Renovation of Berlin Villa, 1988 (Box 1, Volume 2)
  - Bing Overseas Studies Program in the media, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Volume 3)
  - Scrapbook - Overseas Studies (Box 1, Volume 4)
  - Bing Overseas Studies Program in the media, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Volume 5)
  - Historic Photo Collage (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Orientation Handbook - Vienna (Autumn quarter), 1983-1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - PIP Original, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Stanford University Overseas Studies Program Student Handbooks, 1987-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Callie, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - PIP, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - General Info, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Details + Curriculum, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Overseas Studies Orientation Handbook - Oxford (Autumn), 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Stanford University Overseas Studies Program Student Handbooks, 1992-1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Un guia a conocer Chile (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Informational Guide - Latin America (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Stanford a Firenze (Autumn & Spring), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Firenze, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - The Clues Getting on at Oxford (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Orientation Packet - Chile (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Stanford University Overseas Studies Program Student Handbooks, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Orientation Handbook (Moscow & Oxford), 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Stanford Survival Guide for International Undergraduate Students, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Stanford University Overseas Studies Program Student Handbooks, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Ich bin ein Berliner... a guide from students to students, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Student Guidebook (Oxford & Kyoto) (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - SCTI Alumni Directory, 1990-1999 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Para Conocer Chile, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Stanford University Overseas Studies Program Student Handbooks, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Stanford University Overseas Studies Program Student Handbooks, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Berlin Guidebooks, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Que les vaya bien!, 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - aqui Buenos Aires, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Clues, 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - A Guidebook for Stanford Students in Mexico, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Paris for beginners, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Moscow for Beginners, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Benvenuto a Firenze, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Orientation Handbook - Moscow, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Stanford University Overseas Studies Program Student Handbooks, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Student Guidebook/Orientation Packet, 2000-2002 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - BOSP Information Packets, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Stanford University Overseas Studies Program Student Handbooks, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Student Guidebooks/Orientation Packets, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Handbook, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Overseas Studies Program Internal Directory, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Stanford University Overseas Studies Program Student Handbooks (1 of 2), 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Stanford University Overseas Studies Program Student Handbooks (2 of 2), 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Student Guidebooks/Orientation Packets, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Stanford University Overseas Studies Program Student Handbooks, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Student Guidebooks/Orientation Packets (1 of 3), 2002-2004 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Student Guidebooks/Orientation Packets (2 of 3), 2002-2004 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Student Guidebooks/Orientation Packets (3 of 3), 2002-2004 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Program Descriptions (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Fact Sheets, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Flyer (Originals), 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - [Flyers] Originals, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Fact Sheets, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Bing Overseas Photo Contest Submissions (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Germany - Berlin B&W prints, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - SOUS (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Departmental Approvals - Statistical Information (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Overseas Studies Program Documentation/News (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Overseas Studies Program Applications/Enrollments Data, Surveys, 1976-1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - BOSP News (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Program Descriptions/Annual Reports, 1996-1997; 2005-2007 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Overseas Documentation, Letters, Flyers (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Stanford Overseas Studies Program Photobook, 2000-2005 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - C-US Reports (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - CUE: Commission on Undergrad Education (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - OSP Reports (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Report to the Provost of the Committee on Stanford Outside the United States (SOUS), 1996 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Educating American Undergraduates Abroad (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Photos: Wilbur Hall - Cedro; Stern Hall - Holladay House; Stanford Sports, 1955-1956; 1957-1959; 1959 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - OSP Momentos (Berlin, Beijing, & Oxford) (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2016-102
  - Group XI Documents, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ephemera - Tickets, rail passes, etc., circa 1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Event Programs, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Travel Brochures, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2017-026
  - Bing Overseas Studies Calendar, 2016 (Box 1)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2017-165
  - Information for parents & guardians, 1969 Oct 6 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stanford in Germany photograph (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Stanford in Deutschland (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2018-067
  - Palazzo Capponi Inauguration, 2013 May 25 (Box 1)